<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AppSolarSystem</string>
    <string name="drawerTitle">Explore the Solar System</string>
    <string name="drawerAsteroids">Asteroids</string>
    <string name="drawerComets">Comets</string>
    <string name="drawerConstellations">Constellations</string>
    <string name="drawerTheAsteroidBelt">The Asteroid Belt</string>
    <string name="drawerGalaxies">Galaxies</string>
    <string name="drawerStars">Stars</string>
    <string name="formation">Formation</string>
    <string name="distance">Distance, Size and Mass</string>
    <string name="orbit">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="intro">Embark on a journey through the cosmos and discover the wonders of our solar system. Unveil the mysteries of distant planets, their unique landscapes, and the fascinating stories they hold.</string>
    <string name="title">Explore Our Solar System</string>
    <string name="AsteroidIntro">On the first day of January 1801, Giuseppe Piazzi discovered an object which he first thought was a new comet. But after its orbit was better determined it was clear that it was not a comet but more like a small planet. Piazzi named it Ceres, after the Sicilian goddess of grain. Three other small bodies were discovered in the next few years (Pallas, Vesta, and Juno). By the end of the 19th century, there were several hundred.</string>
    <string name="AsteroidHistoryTitle">Asteroid History</string>
    <string name="AsteroidHistory">Several hundred thousand asteroids have been discovered and given provisional designations so far. Thousands more are discovered each year. There are undoubtedly hundreds of thousands more that are too small to be seen from the Earth. There are 26 known asteroids larger than 200 km in diameter. Our census of the largest ones is now fairly complete: we probably know 99% of the asteroids larger than 100 km in diameter. Of those in the 10 to 100 km range we have cataloged about half. But we know very few of the smaller ones; there are probably considerably more than a million asteroids in the 1 km range.  The total mass of all the asteroids is less than that of the Moon.  11 comets and asteroids have been explored by spacecraft so far, as follows: ICE flyby of Comet Giacobini-Zinner. Multiple flyby missions to Comet Halley. Giotto (retarget) to Comet Grigg-Skellerup. Galileo flybys of asteroids Gaspra and Ida (and Ida satellite Dactyl). NEAR-Shoemaker flyby of asteroid Mathilde on the way to orbit and land on Eros. DS-1 flybys of asteroid Braille and Comet Borrelly. Stardust flyby of asteroid Annefrank and recent sample collection from Comet Wild 2. For future we can expect: Hayabusa (MUSES-C) to asteroid Itokawa, Rosetta to Comet Churyumov-Gerasmenko, Deep Impact to Comet Tempel 1, and Dawn to orbit asteroids Vesta and Ceres.</string>
    <string name="AsteroidBeltWhatTitle">What Exactly Is The Asteroid Belt? </string>
    <string name="AsteroidBeltWhatContent"> There are hundreds of thousands of asteroids in the asteroid belt, but almost half of the entire mass is made up of just four objects. These objects are the dwarf planet Ceres, and three other asteroids called Vesta, Pallas and Hygiea. The diameters of Vesta, Pallas and Hygiea are over 400km and Ceres is even bigger at 950km diameter. Of the many thousands of asteroids in the asteroid belt, Ceres is the only one large enough to be classified as a “dwarf planet”. Apart from these four objects, the remaining objects in the asteroid belt range in size from small rocks right down to dust particles.</string>
    <string name="AsteroidBeltHowTitle"> How Far Away Is The Asteroid Belt?</string>
    <string name="AsteroidBeltHowContent"> The asteroid belt is between the planets Mars and Jupiter. It is located about 2.2 to 3.2 Astronomical Units (AU) from the Sun. That is somewhere between 329-478 million km away. The asteroid belt is huge and the space between each of the asteroids is over 600,000 miles. The circumference of Earth is only 24,901.45 miles, which means that the distance between objects in the asteroid belt is more than 24 times the circumference of Earth.</string>

</resources>